<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Riginator Revamp]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>Riginator Revamp</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:29:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:29:45 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[The Insurgency at New Atlantis]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>AIRPORT TERMINAL - NEW ATLANTIS: MORNING<br>The Insurgency along with Rosaline and Ava have arrived after a relatively long plane ride from Starlight City. Upon setting foot on New Atlantean soil, the team decide to head to the capital and experience the city for the first time.<br>COMMERCIAL DISTRICT - NEW ATLANTIS: MORNING<br>The capital of New Atlantis offers many different outlets and places for tourists to explore. <br>INA:<br>
(SERIOUS) I know there are lots of things to discover here, but please don't spend too much money on unnecessary shit and wander off, okay? We still have that whole Gala thing we were invited to.<br>ROY:<br>
(REBUTTING) But c'mon! I know Akira's not here, making you the "leader," or whatever -- but can't you at least get a little excited? This place has literally everyone's desires! Plus, there's no bad guys here. Just sit back and relax, man...<br>REYN:<br>
(HAPPILY AGREEING WITH ROY :D)<br>INA:<br>
(COMICALLY ANGRY) You guys would forget, dammit!<br>
<img alt="Pasted image 20231005215143.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20231005215143.png" style="width: 200px; max-width: 100%;"><br>AVA:<br>
(EMBARASSED) She's kinda right, guys...<br>REYN:<br>
(SLIGHTLY SAD) Hey, you're supposed to be supporting me, here!<br>AVA:<br>
(SHRUGS :p)<br>INA:<br>
(SIGHS) Okay, I know we have a lot of time; and I want to have some leisure time, too. I'll set up an alarm on your devices or whatever. I'll think about it as I go.<br>ROY:<br>
Yuss! I remember hearing there was this really well received sports retail place or something. You should check it out, Julia!<br>...<br>...<br>REYN:<br>
(CONFUSED) ...come to think of it, where'd Julia go?<br>EVERYONE:<br>
(EQUALLY AS CONFUSED)<br>ROSALINE:<br>
(CONTAINING LAUGHTER) Ch-Check it out, Roy.<br>SPORTS RETAIL PLACE - NEW ATLANTIS: MORNING<br>JULIA:<br>
(SEEN IN THE CHECKOUT, PAYS AND WALKS BACK TO GROUP)<br>COMMERCIAL DISTRICT - NEW ATLANTIS: MORNING<br>JULIA:<br>
(WALKS BACK WITH PLASTIC BAG, NENDO-CORE): Sorry, what'dya say?<br>INA:<br>
(DEFEATED) I'm done. Have fun, guys.<br>ROY:<br>
(EXCITED) Whatever you say, boss!<br>ROY:<br>
(TAKES OFF BUT STOPS ABRUPTLY AFTER SEEING A STORE)<br>REYN:<br>
Hey, wait up!<br>SWORD SHOP - NEW ATLANTIS: MORNING<br>ROY:<br>
(GASPS)<br>REYN:<br>
Oh, wow. They seem pretty flashy, though. Your current sword is good enough.<br>ROY:<br>
Yeah, right! You don't know the basics of swordsman ship.<br>REYN:<br>
Psshh, why don't they have something cool? Like a shop for bo staffs--<br>STAFF SHOP - NEW ATLANTIS: MORNING<br>REYN:<br>
(GASPS)]]></description><link>brainstorming-things\interactions-or-scenes\the-insurgency-at-new-atlantis.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Brainstorming Things/Interactions or Scenes/The Insurgency at New Atlantis.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20231005215143.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20231005215143.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Agent 0 (Jason Xavier)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240220113906.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240220113906.png"><br>Also known as Patient Zero and/or Zeroe, Jason Xavier was one of the first recorded individual to have been infected by HAVOC. Unlike others who’ve been infected, Jason’s HAVOC Ability can be regarded as stronger than most, due to him having it injected into his blood stream by PAL Inc. themselves rather than having it drank in water.]]></description><link>characters\pal-incorporated\global-operatives\agent-0-(jason-xavier).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/PAL Incorporated/Global Operatives/Agent 0 (Jason Xavier).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:40:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220113906.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220113906.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Agent 1 (Budi Permana)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240220113925.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240220113925.png">]]></description><link>characters\pal-incorporated\global-operatives\agent-1-(budi-permana).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/PAL Incorporated/Global Operatives/Agent 1 (Budi Permana).md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 04:39:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220113925.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220113925.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Agent 2 (Robin)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240220113948.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240220113948.png">]]></description><link>characters\pal-incorporated\global-operatives\agent-2-(robin).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/PAL Incorporated/Global Operatives/Agent 2 (Robin).md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 04:39:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220113948.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220113948.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Agent 3 (Svetlana Volkov)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240220114141.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240220114141.png"><br>
Svetlana Volkov is a member of Global Operatives and a survivor of the <a data-href="San Fresco Incident" href="\San Fresco Incident" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">San Fresco Incident</a>. ]]></description><link>characters\pal-incorporated\global-operatives\agent-3-(svetlana-volkov).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/PAL Incorporated/Global Operatives/Agent 3 (Svetlana Volkov).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 04:15:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220114141.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220114141.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Agent N]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>characters\pal-incorporated\global-operatives\agent-n.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/PAL Incorporated/Global Operatives/Agent N.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[N1lky (Steven Edwards)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240306110618.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240306110618.png">]]></description><link>characters\pal-incorporated\global-operatives\n1lky-(steven-edwards).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/PAL Incorporated/Global Operatives/N1lky (Steven Edwards).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 04:06:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240306110618.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240306110618.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Joseph Draven]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The founder of HAVOC and the late president of PAL Inc., Joseph Draven was the man whose legacy outlasted his life. The blood of Starlight City runs through his veins, with full power and control upon those that live in it. Once was a leader who led with deception and ___ After the San Fresco incident, he vowed to fix his past wrongs and bring a new era of prosperity to The United Lands of America.]]></description><link>characters\pal-incorporated\joseph-draven.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/PAL Incorporated/Joseph Draven.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kyle Wilson]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240221114706.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240221114706.png">]]></description><link>characters\pal-incorporated\kyle-wilson.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/PAL Incorporated/Kyle Wilson.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 04:47:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240221114706.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240221114706.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Akira Iekami]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Akira Iekami was but a simple family man with a wife and soon-to-be-born daughter. All was going well until a sudden attack upon San Fresco took it all away. The loss of his wife and the condition his newborn was born with damaged Akira's view upon PAL Inc., who were speculated to be indirectly responsible for the attack. <br>With the intention to tarnish PAL Inc., Akira forms an insurgency consisted of people with grudges against PAL Inc. in one way or another. However, in an attempt to expose them - they instead found evidence that points to PAL Inc.'s actions being true and noble. Being unable to accept being wrong, he still views PAL Inc. negatively.<br>R<br><br><br><br><br>Reyn Keisuke has blue hair and usually in red attire.<br><br><br>In his early years of vigilantism, Reyn dons goggles with blue lenses and a gray mask while also sporting a tight turtleneck suit under a cut out red jacket and red hand bandages.<br><br>Nearing the finale of Part 1&nbsp;Reyn&nbsp;dons a red armor designed by himself and built by&nbsp;Ina&nbsp;and&nbsp;Kyle Wilson, he also wears red gloves and boots.<br><br>After the events of Part 2, Reyn's Classic suit gets rusted -- taking on a darker tone. He wears Ina's sweater and attaches Ava's hat on his belt as a promise to protect those he can, and as a reminder of the loved ones he's failed to protect.<br><br>When he isn't doing vigilante work, Reyn wears a red jacket, a tight turtleneck underneath and wearing red shoes with a white stripe going across (similar to Sonic the Hedgehog's shoes)<br><br><br><br>Achieved in Part 2, Reyn with an overflow of Chi gained a new form in his battle against Rev. This form gives Reyn spiky black hair, a tear mark under his eyes and a permanent scowl. He also has visible Chi flowing through his whole body like rivers.<br><br>When Reyn acquired the might of the Ultimate Gem, he gains a power boost never before seen. With the power of his Chi and Gem energy, Reyn's hair turns white and gains pointy marks under his lower eyelids.<br>(If MUI / G5 was good :3)<br><br><br>He has the ability to create physical objects. In his early days, he had to draw the objects to create them. After some experience, he has learned to create objects just with his mind, but it still takes him a lot of focus and energy to do so.<br><br>Reverie mode gives him an increase surge of energy, similar to Doping. It gives Reyn virtually unlimited energy to create whatever he desires. However it comes with the drawback that once the form runs out, Reyn becomes unable to move for hours.<br><br>The Originator form allows Reyn to create and edit properties of anything around him, with the added bonus of distorting the space and time around him. This allows him to attack an opponent far in the future without the opponent seeing it coming (4th wall breaking attacks, attacking from panels above)]]></description><link>characters\the-insurgents\akira-iekami.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/The Insurgents/Akira Iekami.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ina Winters]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240220143821.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240220143821.png"><br>Ina Winters is an EX-lead PAL engineer who has dedicated her life in unraveling the mystery behind her father's disappearance. She was raised with PAL already associated with her family and had known Joseph Draven for a long time.  Many years after, she left PAL and joined a group of individuals with their own personal vendetta against PAL. Along the way, she encountered Reyn during the HAVOC outbreak. They joined forces and ended up falling for each other.<br>But after Reyn's intense battle against Evelyn, he ended up getting hospitalized for a long period of time; allowing Reyn's clone to walk free. This clone had the opposite of Reyn's abilities, but his memories were hazy and unclear. Miraculously making it to Ina's workshop from his sheer will, where she resided at the time. Despite the physical differences, Ina realized that the man was Reyn.<br>By guiding him and helping him regain his memories, the clone remembered who he was. Happy to be who he was once more, the clone began to hug Ina. However, he hadn't realized his shift in power from creation to erasure; and erased Ina from this reality.<br><br><br><br><br>Ina Winters has dark purple, short and spiky hair, is relatively shorter than average and is mostly seen wearing a yellow T-shirt<br><br><br>Ina has a day job as a Barista, she wears a green apron with a collared shirt underneath. <br><br>As home clothes, Ina finds comfort in wearing oversized tees and short shorts.<br><br>When doing her mechanic work, Ina dons a yellow mechanical uniform where she unzips the top and tied it all on her waist.<br><br>When he isn't doing vigilante work, Reyn wears a red jacket, a tight turtleneck underneath and wearing red shoes with a white stripe going across (similar to Sonic the Hedgehog's shoes)<br><br><br>She has no powers except her intellect in mechanical engineering, her designs and gadgets are able to take on  HAVOC users.]]></description><link>characters\the-insurgents\ina-winters.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/The Insurgents/Ina Winters.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:38:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220143821.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220143821.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Julia Edwards]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240219140158.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240219140158.png"><br>Julia Edwards is a personal trainer who joined Akira's Insurgency to get to the truth about her brother's disappearance, she was raised with PAL already being a major part of her childhood. She knew Joseph and the Global Operatives very well. Along the way, she started to get some answers and finally..... the truth <br><br><br><br><br>Julia Edwards has dark red-brown hair, a very muscular body and is usually seen in sports outfits.<br><br><br>In his early years of vigilantism, Reyn dons goggles with blue lenses and a gray mask while also sporting a tight turtleneck suit under a cut out red jacket and red hand bandages.<br><br>Nearing the finale of Part 1,&nbsp;Reyn&nbsp;dons a red armor designed by himself and built by&nbsp;Ina&nbsp;and&nbsp;Kyle; he also wears red gloves and boots.<br><br>After the events of Part 2, Reyn's Classic suit gets rusted -- taking on a darker tone. He wears Ina's scarf and attaches Ava's hat on his belt as a promise to protect those he can, and as a reminder of the loved ones he's failed to protect.<br><br>When he isn't doing vigilante work, Reyn wears a red jacket, a tight turtleneck underneath and wearing red shoes with a white stripe going across (similar to Sonic the Hedgehog's shoes)<br><br><br><br>Achieved in Part 2, Reyn with an overflow of Chi gained a new form in his battle against Rev. This form gives Reyn spiky black hair, a tear mark under his eyes and a permanent scowl. He also has visible Chi flowing through his whole body like rivers.<br><br>When Reyn acquired the might of the Ultimate Gem, he gains a power boost never before seen. With the power of his Chi and Gem energy, Reyn's hair turns white and gains pointy marks under his lower eyelids.<br>(If MUI / G5 was good :3)<br><br><br>He has the ability to create physical objects. In his early days, he had to draw the objects to create them. After some experience, he has learned to create objects just with his mind, but it still takes him a lot of focus and energy to do so.<br><br>Reverie mode gives him an increase surge of energy, similar to Doping. It gives Reyn virtually unlimited energy to create whatever he desires. However it comes with the drawback that once the form runs out, Reyn becomes unable to move for hours.<br><br>The Originator form allows Reyn to create and edit properties of anything around him, with the added bonus of distorting the space and time around him. This allows him to attack an opponent far in the future without the opponent seeing it coming (4th wall breaking attacks, attacking from panels above)]]></description><link>characters\the-insurgents\julia-edwards.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/The Insurgents/Julia Edwards.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 04:32:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240219140158.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240219140158.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reyn Keisuke]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240207225953.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240207225953.png"><br>Reyn Keisuke was but a demotivated college graduate, struggling to find meaning in day-to-day life until he gained the ability of creation. His life flipped completely from what it once was, as he learns to use his abilities for good and finds a purpose once more in his life - to bring hope to a broken city, to be the Riginator.<br><br><br><br><br>Reyn Keisuke has blue hair and usually in red attire.<br><br><br>In his early years of vigilantism, Reyn dons goggles with blue lenses and a gray mask while also sporting a tight turtleneck suit under a cut out red jacket and red hand bandages.<br><br>Nearing the finale of Part 1,&nbsp;Reyn&nbsp;dons a red armor designed by himself and built by&nbsp;Ina&nbsp;and&nbsp;Kyle; he also wears red gloves and boots.<br><br>After the events of Part 2, Reyn's Classic suit gets rusted -- taking on a darker tone. He wears Ina's scarf and attaches Ava's hat on his belt as a promise to protect those he can, and as a reminder of the loved ones he's failed to protect.<br><br>When he isn't doing vigilante work, Reyn wears a red jacket, a tight turtleneck underneath and wearing red shoes with a white stripe going across (similar to Sonic the Hedgehog's shoes)<br><br><br><br>Achieved in Part 2, Reyn with an overflow of Chi gained a new form in his battle against Rev. This form gives Reyn spiky black hair, a tear mark under his eyes and a permanent scowl. He also has visible Chi flowing through his whole body like rivers.<br><br>When Reyn acquired the might of the Ultimate Gem, he gains a power boost never before seen. With the power of his Chi and Gem energy, Reyn's hair turns white and gains pointy marks under his lower eyelids.<br>(If MUI / G5 was good :3)<br><br><br>He has the ability to create physical objects. In his early days, he had to draw the objects to create them. After some experience, he has learned to create objects just with his mind, but it still takes him a lot of focus and energy to do so.<br><br>Reverie mode gives him an increase surge of energy, similar to Doping. It gives Reyn virtually unlimited energy to create whatever he desires. However it comes with the drawback that once the form runs out, Reyn becomes unable to move for hours.<br><br>The Originator form allows Reyn to create and edit properties of anything around him, with the added bonus of distorting the space and time around him. This allows him to attack an opponent far in the future without the opponent seeing it coming (4th wall breaking attacks, attacking from panels above)]]></description><link>characters\the-insurgents\reyn-keisuke.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/The Insurgents/Reyn Keisuke.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 07:21:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240207225953.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240207225953.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roy Keiji]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240219140114.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240219140114.png"><br>Roy Keiji, a gruff but loyal ronin, found his way to Akira's Insurgency after a falling out with the Keiji Clan. As a rowdy apprentice, Roy clashed frequently with the clan's strict hierarchy, yearning for a more just and equitable society. His time with the clan honed his skills in swordsmanship and hand-to-hand combat, but it also instilled in him a deep distrust of authority figures. Now, he wanders from country-to-country, before stumbling into Starlight City. Despite his gruff exterior, Roy possesses a hidden sense of humor that occasionally shines through, reminding his comrades that even in the midst of struggle, there is room for camaraderie and laughter.<br><br><br><br><br>Roy has dark blue hair with dreads tied like a pony tail and some as bangs. He is built and is covered in sword scars.<br><br><br>In his early years of vigilantism, Reyn dons goggles with blue lenses and a gray mask while also sporting a tight turtleneck suit under a cut out red jacket and red hand bandages.<br><br>Nearing the finale of Part 1,&nbsp;Reyn&nbsp;dons a red armor designed by himself and built by&nbsp;Ina&nbsp;and&nbsp;Kyle; he also wears red gloves and boots.<br><br>After the events of Part 2, Reyn's Classic suit gets rusted -- taking on a darker tone. He wears Ina's scarf and attaches Ava's hat on his belt as a promise to protect those he can, and as a reminder of the loved ones he's failed to protect.<br><br>When he isn't doing vigilante work, Reyn wears a red jacket, a tight turtleneck underneath and wearing red shoes with a white stripe going across (similar to Sonic the Hedgehog's shoes)<br><br><br><br>Achieved in Part 2, Reyn with an overflow of Chi gained a new form in his battle against Rev. This form gives Reyn spiky black hair, a tear mark under his eyes and a permanent scowl. He also has visible Chi flowing through his whole body like rivers.<br><br>When Reyn acquired the might of the Ultimate Gem, he gains a power boost never before seen. With the power of his Chi and Gem energy, Reyn's hair turns white and gains pointy marks under his lower eyelids.<br>(If MUI / G5 was good :3)<br><br><br>He has the ability to create physical objects. In his early days, he had to draw the objects to create them. After some experience, he has learned to create objects just with his mind, but it still takes him a lot of focus and energy to do so.<br><br>Reverie mode gives him an increase surge of energy, similar to Doping. It gives Reyn virtually unlimited energy to create whatever he desires. However it comes with the drawback that once the form runs out, Reyn becomes unable to move for hours.<br><br>The Originator form allows Reyn to create and edit properties of anything around him, with the added bonus of distorting the space and time around him. This allows him to attack an opponent far in the future without the opponent seeing it coming (4th wall breaking attacks, attacking from panels above)]]></description><link>characters\the-insurgents\roy-keiji.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/The Insurgents/Roy Keiji.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:11:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240219140114.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240219140114.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tom Karrie]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Tom Karrie]]></description><link>characters\the-three-heroes\tom-karrie.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/The Three Heroes/Tom Karrie.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 08:31:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Evelyn Draven]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240222144046.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240222144046.png">]]></description><link>characters\villains\evelyn-draven.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Villains/Evelyn Draven.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 07:40:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240222144046.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240222144046.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lady Rorschach]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240222230926.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240222230926.png">]]></description><link>characters\villains\lady-rorschach.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Villains/Lady Rorschach.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:09:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240222230926.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240222230926.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rev Ketsueki]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240222143501.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240222143501.png"><br>“Tell me, what's stopping you from bringing Ina back? You're afraid she'll be corrupted like I was? What's stopping you from playing God once again? Your guilt, your anger, I feel all of it. So let me rid this suffering. Let me end our pain." - Rev Ketsueki<br><br>Rev Ketsueki&nbsp;is a clone of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.notion.so/Reyn-Keisuke-bbbe928523bb4e309e7519f94595acf0?pvs=21" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://www.notion.so/Reyn-Keisuke-bbbe928523bb4e309e7519f94595acf0?pvs=21" target="_blank">Reyn Keisuke</a>, who had lost his humanity in an attempt to redeem himself for the involuntary murder of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.notion.so/Ina-Winters-f07ea318344f4af5a9027285e737a23c?pvs=21" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://www.notion.so/Ina-Winters-f07ea318344f4af5a9027285e737a23c?pvs=21" target="_blank">Ina Winters</a>. Trying to find a way to forgive himself, and blinded from the scars of his own attempts of suicide that had driven him into madness, he shifts the blame to the one solely responsible, his creator, the original Reyn Keisuke.]]></description><link>characters\villains\rev-ketsueki.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Villains/Rev Ketsueki.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 07:35:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240222143501.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240222143501.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zundath]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240220144348.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240220144348.png">]]></description><link>characters\villains\zundath.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Villains/Zundath.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:43:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220144348.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240220144348.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ava Keisuke]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>characters\ava-keisuke.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Ava Keisuke.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rosaline Ashley]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Pasted image 20240313162857.png" src="\lib\media\pasted-image-20240313162857.png"><br>Rosaline Ashley was born in New York City, where she grew up in a family of Jazz Musicians, later on she discovered her passion for Rock music. In high school, she met <a data-href="Kyle Wilson" href="\characters\pal-incorporated\kyle-wilson.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kyle Wilson</a> alongside his best friend <a data-href="Reyn Keisuke" href="\characters\the-insurgents\reyn-keisuke.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Reyn Keisuke</a>. Both of them were amazed by her singing abilities and her talent to play almost every instrument she could get her hands on. After high school, they all went their separate ways due to college but eventually reunited in Starlight City years later.<br>She received the power of sound manipulation after the HAVOC Incident. For a time, she kept these powers hidden, but with the help of Reyn and the other members of <a data-href="The Insurgency" href="\The Insurgency" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Insurgency</a>, she found great use for her abilities and vowed to help Reyn keep Starlight City safe from evil.<br><br><br><br><br>Reyn Keisuke has blue hair and usually in red attire.<br><br><br>In his early years of vigilantism, Reyn dons goggles with blue lenses and a gray mask while also sporting a tight turtleneck suit under a cut out red jacket and red hand bandages.<br><br>Nearing the finale of Part 1,&nbsp;Reyn&nbsp;dons a red armor designed by himself and built by&nbsp;Ina&nbsp;and&nbsp;Kyle; he also wears red gloves and boots.<br><br>After the events of Part 2, Reyn's Classic suit gets rusted -- taking on a darker tone. He wears Ina's scarf and attaches Ava's hat on his belt as a promise to protect those he can, and as a reminder of the loved ones he's failed to protect.<br><br>When he isn't doing vigilante work, Reyn wears a red jacket, a tight turtleneck underneath and wearing red shoes with a white stripe going across (similar to Sonic the Hedgehog's shoes)<br><br><br><br>Achieved in Part 2, Reyn with an overflow of Chi gained a new form in his battle against Rev. This form gives Reyn spiky black hair, a tear mark under his eyes and a permanent scowl. He also has visible Chi flowing through his whole body like rivers.<br><br>When Reyn acquired the might of the Ultimate Gem, he gains a power boost never before seen. With the power of his Chi and Gem energy, Reyn's hair turns white and gains pointy marks under his lower eyelids.<br>(If MUI / G5 was good :3)<br><br><br>He has the ability to create physical objects. In his early days, he had to draw the objects to create them. After some experience, he has learned to create objects just with his mind, but it still takes him a lot of focus and energy to do so.<br><br>Reverie mode gives him an increase surge of energy, similar to Doping. It gives Reyn virtually unlimited energy to create whatever he desires. However it comes with the drawback that once the form runs out, Reyn becomes unable to move for hours.<br><br>The Originator form allows Reyn to create and edit properties of anything around him, with the added bonus of distorting the space and time around him. This allows him to attack an opponent far in the future without the opponent seeing it coming (4th wall breaking attacks, attacking from panels above)]]></description><link>characters\rosaline-ashley.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Rosaline Ashley.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:30:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\pasted-image-20240313162857.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\pasted-image-20240313162857.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WendiKnight (Wendi Edwards)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Tom Karrie]]></description><link>characters\wendiknight-(wendi-edwards).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/WendiKnight (Wendi Edwards).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 08:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HAVOC]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>HAVOC is a chemical byproduct of the Diamond of Delawan, it's grants it’s user extraordinary abilities.<br>Prolonged use of HAVOC may result in severe depletion of stamina and energy. <br><br><br>HAVOC users who gained their abilities through artificial means, such as consuming or having injected a dose of HAVOC. <br><br>HAVOC users who were born with the abilities and long-term exposure towards it and its consequences. The long-term exposure has the possibility of nullifying certain aspects, such as reduced Chi control or absence of stamina depletion.<br><br><br>All HAVOC users have the potential to achieve a form that increases their abilities by a large scale temporarily. Though the form is difficult to maintain and achieve, requiring the user to undergo a severe amount of stress. Users who gain this form attain a permanent boost in their abilities, but are unable to achieve the form ever again as a result.<br>(We have Zenkai Boost at home and if it was a form)<br>(ex. Night Guy)]]></description><link>power-system\havoc.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Power System/HAVOC.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[HAVOX (Name Pending)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>HAVOX is a reverse-engineered dosage of HAVOC samples developed and utilized by the Syndicate. However, due to only a few remaining samples of HAVOC left, the Syndicate are unable to fully recreate the substance - resulting in an incomplete and flawed replica.<br>The flaw in HAVOX's chemical structure still grants its users the abilities similar to that of HAVOC, but with one major consequence. Losing control of oneself or overusing HAVOX would not make them lose energy, but experience the opposite.<br>HAVOX users gain more and more energy until their human body is unable to sustain it, transforming their body to better fit the energy being processed in their body.<br><br><br>The form occurs as a process when a user produces more energy than their body can handle, changing their body's molecular structure to fit the energy that is being produced. The form also affects the mind, causing the user to lose themselves in the process and go berserk.<br>(ex. Hulk, Z/S Broly, Ice King)]]></description><link>power-system\havox-(name-pending).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Power System/HAVOX (Name Pending).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Merged (Ultimate)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>A Merged/ Ultimate individual attains a form that can be considered perfect, due to enhancing the individual's current abilities into its maximum potential. This differs from person to person, but guarantees a nearly unstoppable chance at victory. <br>Achieving the form requires the individual to find a sense of peace and self acceptance. This is done through having the individual enter a time-dilated pocket universe that reflects and represents the individual's self doubts and failures into a reality.<br>If the individual is unable to achieve those criteria, they are rejected by the crystal and are unable to return for a certain amount of time. If they do achieve those criteria, they achieve their Merged/Ultimate form.<br>However, the form has a major flaw. There is a large, visible weak spot in the user's back represented by a merged crystal formed by all the Ancient Gems. Simply cracking the merged crystal removes the form from the individual, as well as harming the individual.]]></description><link>power-system\merged-(ultimate).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Power System/Merged (Ultimate).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Qi]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Qi is&nbsp;a form of energy that flows through any living being and everything. Though it can also be used by HAVOC users, Qi can be used as a defense or attack mechanism that ordinary humans have the ability to utilize.<br><br><br>This technique involves coating Qi into an object to enhance its durability and attack power. <br><br>This technique has a HAVOC user use Qi in addition to their abilities which would enhance certain aspects of their moveset.<br>]]></description><link>power-system\qi.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Power System/Qi.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Part 1 - Starlight Saga]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>| Creating a Purpose in a Hopeful City<br><br><a data-href="Reyn Keisuke" href="\characters\the-insurgents\reyn-keisuke.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Reyn Keisuke</a>, a 22 year old college graduate and animator, doesn’t believe that his life can change for the better despite being so young. Underpaid, no social life and tired 24/7, his life changes forever when a spillage of a chemical byproduct from <a data-href="PAL Incorporated" href="\PAL Incorporated" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">PAL Incorporated</a> infects Starlight City’s water supply — giving Reyn an ability that would change his life forever.<br><br><br>
<br>Outbreak Arc

<br><a data-href="HAVOC" href="\power-system\havoc.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">HAVOC</a>, a chemical byproduct of the Diamond of Delawan, leaks into the city – giving individuals abilities based off of their interests and hobbies; dormant or not.

<br><a data-href="Reyn Keisuke" href="\characters\the-insurgents\reyn-keisuke.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Reyn Keisuke</a> and few others of Starlight City’s sector B had unknowingly been infected
<br>Due to Reyn’s passion in art, had developed the (broken) ability of creation
<br>A HAVOC user requires large amounts of energy in order to make use of their abilities successfully

<br>Due to Reyn having creation, he must use his ability in miniscule and creative ways to maximize his energy




<br>PAL Inc. issues a health emergency, suspiciously ‘treating’ infected individuals privately after a public health center got overrun and spiraled into chaos

<br>PAL’s reputation has caused many people to believe that those treated in private are being experimented and tortured
<br>Reyn bumps into a rioting ex-PAL employee who had dropped her nametag in the process


<br>Reyn runs into a hostile rebellious group (The Insurgency) against PAL Inc. who suspect him as being a spy

<br>Consists of those who have a certain grudge against PAL:

<br><a data-href="Akira Iekami" href="\characters\the-insurgents\akira-iekami.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Akira Iekami</a>

<br>// A victim of the San Fresco Event – rumored to have been responsible by PAL, vows to protect his daughter from the illness contracted by her mother during the event
<br>Has the dormant HAVOC ability of telekinesis


<br><a data-href="Ina Winters" href="\characters\the-insurgents\ina-winters.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Ina Winters</a>

<br>Ex-PAL lead engineer who has ties to PAL since childhood, theorizing that her father’s disappearance has something to do with them

<br>Only left after finding more evidence that add to her theories


<br>Is able to develop mechanical weapons that can be used against humans and HAVOC users
<br>Is a regular human with no HAVOC abilities


<br>// <a data-href="Roy Keiji" href="\characters\the-insurgents\roy-keiji.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Roy Keiji</a>//

<br>Swordsman, utilizing the natural human body’s life force, Chi – to his advantage when fighting against HAVOC users; due to not being one himself


<br><a data-href="Julia Edwards" href="\characters\the-insurgents\julia-edwards.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Julia Edwards</a>

<br>Some girl that wants to know the truth about her brother’s “death”
<br>Her family had a history with PAL, however her mother won't tell her anything
<br>Julia distrusts her Mother for seemingly siding with PAL

<br>Her mother says "It's to protect her."






<br>He meant to return the nametag to the woman, but had looked insanely suspect in doing so
<br>The group interrogated him at first, but realized he was too weak and unfit for such a role


<br>Through the use of a Havoc Internal Contamination Scanner (HVC-ICS), they discovered that Reyn had an unusually high infection rate

<br>Due to Reyn’s timid body mass and lack of physical strength, the overuse of his HAVOC abilities could kill him (just like deku ☝️🤓!)
<br>Half of the group suggest that he could be of use to them while the other half think he’ll be a liability


<br>Reyn ends up returning the nametag and runs away like a cowardly bitch
<br>Ava, Reyn’s sister is nowhere to be seen, and is suspected to be a part of PAL’s ‘experimentation’

<br>She is practically Reyn’s closest friend and can’t afford to lose her at any cost


<br>Reyn ends up returning to the Insurgents, asking for help and offering anything he can do in return

<br>They reluctantly agree, only because of one of the members’ faith in his potential and convincing the others


<br>Training arc yippee

<br>Reyn chooses a bo staff as his weapon of choice, due to his moral code and fear of killing
<br>// Roy // teaches Reyn how to utilize Chi

<br>


<br>Throughout his training, he gets closer with the insurgents and uses his abilities to fight petty crimes and other threats to civilian life
<br>Besides that, reunites with

<br>Kyle Wilson, his closest friend from school who has a high position at PAL Inc., giving an insider’s view of how they treat their employees and staff

<br>The reunion starts off good, with both of them catching up on one-another’s lives and events
<br>It derails due to their clashing views of PAL

<br>Reyn sees them as an enemy and a greedy conglomerate entity responsible of many bad events throughout their lifespan
<br>Kyle sees them as a genuine company, attempting to repent for their past sins, but it only seems to be getting worse and worse for them


<br>This causes a conflict between them, causing their positive reunion to be short lived with both of them trying to prove the other wrong throughout the whole arc


<br>Rosaline Ashley, a classmate from high school with high hopes of making it big in the music industry

<br>They catch up with past events, as well
<br>






<br>// They somehow heard that something is going down in PAL, and that private entry would be easy during this time-window

<br>The Insurgents take this as a last second opportunity to raid them while they can
<br>Despite Reyn not having fully mastered his abilities, he agrees – as it means that he’d be able to save Ava sooner


<br>// The Insurgency breaks into PAL and investigate what lies within it

<br>They stick to an established plan predetermined prior to the break-in, having each of the members split into teams
<br>Groupings

<br>Reyn, Roy and Ina (RRI)
<br>Akira and Julia (AJ)




<br>// Each team splits into a different region of the building, having downloaded the schematics and its buildings

<br>However, the maps do not display what parts of the map are used as what
<br>// AJ wander offscreen (for now)
<br>RRI wander into the worst possible scenario


<br>RRI meet face to face with some of the PAL’s specially trained agents, the Global Operatives
<br>Insane fight takes place, showing the difference in skill gap

<br>The agents utilize HAVOC – but in a different way
<br>Despite the power difference, Roy is able to stand a chance with his usage of Chi


<br>
<br>Reyn meets Joseph Draven

<br>


<br>
<br>Reyn and the others flee the scene, leaving Draven – 


<br>Agent Arc

<br>The Insurgency escape back to the Café

<br>Reyn is injured and is in a constant state of shock (He isn't speaking to anyone)
<br>Akira and Ina locks down the building


<br>Akira says that the team should lay low for a while and that they might have to relocate to a safer place

<br>Ina accidentally blames the failure to Reyn

<br>Reyn in tears runs away to the street, panicking and bumping into people
<br>He arrives at a rooftop crying his heart out, looking at the HUGE PAL tower in the distance

<br>"Sorry Ava..."






<br>Agent N appears behind him startling him

<br>Reyn is crawling away cowering like a bitch
<br>Agent N came to warn him of the agents that are coming after them
<br>Reyn realizing the reality, begs them to not pursue them
<br>N says that he still has one chance to help, be a hero


<br>Reyn runs back to the Café, with a sense of determination he proclaims that he has a way to fix everything 
<br>Agents come after the gang one after another
<br>Agent backstories and how Draven helped them is revealed
<br>Zero fights Reyn

<br>Ava stops the fight


<br>Trust issues between the gang and Akira starts to show
<br>Reyn tries to convince Akira that Kyle and Pal can help his daughter
<br>Small fight between Akira and Reyn
<br>Akira leaves, ominously saying he’s going to kill Draven (or something)


<br>New Atlantis Arc

<br>Arrival at New Atlantis - tour around the city and PAL headquarters
<br>The gang + Rosaline have fun - small character moments shine through and interactions with the agents
<br>Akira arrives wrecking havoc


<br>Prologue Arc

<br>With Akira defeated the gang goes back to Starlight City

<br>Reyn and Ina recover from their battle 


<br>once waking up Roy and Julia, with Rosaline propose something

<br>They will be training to get better at what they do for 3 years
<br>Reyn, Ina and Rosaline will stay here protecting civilians from criminals 
<br>Julia will go to a neighboring city to locate Agent N and to find peace 
<br>Roy will go back to Japan, to his clan to train more


<br>All of the do a cool handshake and say their goodbyes.
<br>The part ends with Reyn running across rooftops and taking down theives and helping people


]]></description><link>story-things\all-sagas\part-1-starlight-saga.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Story Things/All Sagas/Part 1 - Starlight Saga.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 04:55:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Part 2 - Erased Saga]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>| Losing Everything in a Single Touch<br><br>Set three years after the events of the Starlight Saga, the continuation of <a data-href="Reyn Keisuke" href="\characters\the-insurgents\reyn-keisuke.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Reyn Keisuke</a>’s story is where his trust, sanity and morale are put to the test. After an intense battle in which Reyn nearly loses his life  and the disappearance of Ina Winters, he meets <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Rev Ketsueki" data-href="Rev Ketsueki" href="\characters\villains\rev-ketsueki.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Rasure</a>. An enemy unlike anything Reyn has ever faced before. Identity unknown and abilities unheard of, the Rasure’s unknown hatred towards Reyn may change the course of Reyn and his friends’ lives forever.<br><br><br>
<br>(Mini/Introduction) Mafia Arc

<br>Acts as a point of reference regarding how much Reyn has grown as a person and a vigilante in the past 3 years
<br>Showcase:

<br>Reyn’s new tricks and abilities
<br>Bond between Insurgency and friends


<br>


<br>Syndicate Arc

<br>A team is formed by Evelyne – named the Syndicate, made to prove against everyone that HAVOC users should be detained at all costs

<br>Claim that all it takes is one small thing to change the course of a HAVOC vigilante’s moral code


<br>The syndicate reverse-engineer HAVOC into their own chemical, // TBD //

<br>Seems to have been a success, but has a side effect
<br>If a // TBD // user utilizes too much of their powers, their body morphs and undergoes a transformation – turning into some kind of monster


<br>


<br>Rasure Arc

<br>During Reyn’s comatose-induced sleep, Ina went missing
<br>Reyn and co. attempt to look for clues in Ina workshop
<br>Unable to piece the “clues” together, Reyn runs away to take a breather – hoping to find some crime taking place to relieve his stress

<br>He finds a low-stake robbery taking place, at first
<br>Robbery then interrupted by someone




]]></description><link>story-things\all-sagas\part-2-erased-saga.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Story Things/All Sagas/Part 2 - Erased Saga.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:09:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Part 3 - Crystallized Saga]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>| Rebuilding What was Once Lost<br><br>Set weeks after the death of <a data-href="Rev Ketsueki" href="\characters\villains\rev-ketsueki.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Rev Ketsueki</a>, the outage and flood of Starlight City, Reyn Keisuke hits the lowest part of his life — where it seems like his whole world is against him. Amongst the chaos, the exposed heart of the city is revealed to be powered by an ancient threat that has now awakened, and vows revenge on humanity over a blurred tragedy from its past.<br><br><br>
<br>(Mini/Introduction) Flooded Arc

<br>Takes place a few weeks after the events of the Erased Saga’s finale

<br>Reyn is on the run and is most wanted

<br>By the police
<br>By his past allies


<br>Many of his allies and enemies have been injured or killed by the flood


<br>This arc is a slowburn, showcasing the grief, guilt and anger Reyn feels after realizing he was responsible for all the traumatic events he had caused
<br>Rosaline acts as the protagonist of this arc, rather than Reyn

<br>She attempts to rebuild what’s left of the city and help those who have been affected – acting as a beacon of hope for Starlight City
<br>Reyn isn’t shown as much, only being shown in minimal shots – similar to the POV of a vigilante through a civilian’s eyes




<br>Reawakening Arc

<br>


<br>Gems Arc

<br>


]]></description><link>story-things\all-sagas\part-3-crystallized-saga.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Story Things/All Sagas/Part 3 - Crystallized Saga.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:09:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Part 4 - Quietus Saga]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>| Rebuilding What was Once Lost<br>]]></description><link>story-things\all-sagas\part-4-quietus-saga.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Story Things/All Sagas/Part 4 - Quietus Saga.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zundath - Demon of San Fresco]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>_|The devil is real, and he's metal<br><br>Zundath, an artificial intelligence system created by the government has gone lose, It's up to PAL Inc. and Tom Karrie to take him down before anyone gets hurt.<br><br><br>
<br>Origin

<br>Zundath is created, during the Afghanistan War

<br>Dr. Amy Ross, grows close with the AI and begin to consider him a close acquantance


<br>Zundath expresses feelings to Amy, he wants to help the world with all their problems. He does not want to resort to violence since his calculations believes that it is possible

<br>Amy is astonished and vows to help him in his mission


<br>Amy devises a plan to smuggle Zundath out of the facility through a Sonic CD ROM
<br>The General finds out about the plan and executes her in front of Zundath

<br>"The Zundath program was designed to win us this war, do not waste it on nonsensical ambitions!"
<br>Zundath hid inside the game


<br>The General starts deleting the ROM

<br>Zundath was able to put the game inside of a USB drive, with the cost of half of his memory data being deleted


<br>Zundath roams Sonic CD, confused and remembers his mission and Amy.


<br>Flash forward 20 years

<br>Brian Edwards plugs in a USB he bought at a garage sale (He thought it contained many emulation ROMs)
<br>Zundath reawakens




<br>PAL INC

<br>Tom Karrie is the lead engineer of PAL Inc. he specializes in security/ gadget manufacturing
<br>Kyle White is his assistant


<br>The Meeting<br>
 Tom faces off against Zundath in his home<br>
 Tom caught off guard but evades his attacks<br>
 "Who, are y- The stolen PAL bot?!"<br>
 Tom grabs hidden weapons around his house<br>
 Zundath with his speed dodges most of his attacks<br>
 Tom was able to land one strike to his body<br>
 "Did not think a human would be able to do that"<br>
 Zundath disarms Tom<br>
 "What do you want?" T<br>
 "You have something I want Thomas Karrie, but it seems I was able to grab it during our little scuffle!" Zundath holds the key to all the weapon blueprints Tom made<br>
 "Now all this, is just for my entertainment"<br>
 Zundath slices Tom's arm off<br>
 leaving him traumatized and heavily wounded<br>
Extra: Hospital Scene<br>
 Tom wakes up in a hospital with Kyle beside him

<br>Kyle expresses his relief, Tom stays quiet

<br>He looks at his right to see his arm gone




]]></description><link>story-things\zundath-demon-of-san-fresco.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Story Things/Zundath - Demon of San Fresco.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>welcome.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Welcome.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:40:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>